Guide to the Elena Wilson Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1971-1979; Series II; 7.71; (19 boxes)
  - LETTERS ON LITERATURE AND POLITICS
    - Photocopies of Edmund Wilson Correspondence
      - Smith, Norman Kemp (1916-56), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 580)
        Includes Born, Max
      - Soule, George Henry
      - The Southern Review
      - Steegmuller, Francis (1955-70), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 581)
      - Stein, Gertrude (1923-42), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 582)
        Includes Van Vechten, Carl
      - Steloff, Frances (1938-61), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 583)
      - Stern, James (1940 Dec), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 584)
      - Straus, Roger W. (1950-72), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 585-586)
        Includes Peck, John B.
        Includes Straus, Dorothea
        See also: Austin, John E., box 10, folder 331
      - Strong, L. A. G. (Leonard Alfred George) (1929 Oct 23), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 587)
      - Struve, Gleb (1949-62), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 588)
      - Sutherland, Donald (1952 Apr 9) (Box 20, Folder 589)
      - Tate, Allen (1923-62, n.d.), 1974, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 590-592)
      - Thoby-Marcelin, Philippe (1948-71, n.d.) (Box 20, Folder 593-594)
        Includes Thoby-Marcelin, Eva
      - Thomas, Issac (1942 Jul-Oct), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 595)
      - Thorp, Willard (1944 Dec 18), 1974, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 596)
      - Thurber, James (1942-59), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 597)
      - Tindall, William York (1940-42) (Box 20, Folder 598)
      - Troxell, Gilbert McCoy (1918-58, n.d.) (Box 20, Folder 599)
        Includes original ALS
        Includes Belknap, Morris
        Includes Hamilton, David Osborne
        Includes Noyes, Larry G.
        Includes Troxell, Janet Camp
      - Turner, Arlin (1949-60), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 600)
      - Untermeyer, Louis (1957 Aug 13), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 601)
      - Viereck, Peter (1950-65, n.d.) (Box 21, Folder 602)
        Includes Viereck, Anya
        Includes Viereck, George Sylvester
      - The Virginia Quarterly Review (1930-46), 1973, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 603)
      - W. H. Allen (1956-58), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 604)
      - W. W. Norton & Company (1937-41), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 605)
      - Wain, John (1968, n.d.) (Box 21, Folder 606)
      - Walden, Harriet (1964-72), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 607)
      - Walker, Charles Rumford (1917-71, n.d.) (Box 21, Folder 608)
        Includes "Lisa"
      - Warren, Robert Penn (1941-60), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 609)
      - Warshow, Robert (1946-52), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 610)
      - Wartels, Nat (1957 Dec 18), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 611)
      - Wensinger, Arthur S. (1968 Mar 2), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 612)
      - Wheelock John H.
        See: Perkins, Maxwell E. (Maxwell Evarts), box 19, folders 449-450
      - Whitaker, Rogers E. M.
      - White, Katharine Sergeant Angell (1929-72), 1973, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 613)
      - Wilder, Thornton (1940 Jun 20), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 614)
      - Willcox, Bertram F. (1970 Feb), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 615)
      - Wilson, Angus (1950-66), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 616)
        Includes typed transcript
        Includes "Tony"
      - Winkelhorn, Sofka (1951-58), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 617)
        Includes Winkelhorn, Kai
      - Wolfe, Bertram David (1940-58), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 618)
      - Wood, Peggy (1942 May 27), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 619)
      - Woodward, Mrs. (1942 Feb 9), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 620)
      - Woollcott, Alexander (1941 Feb-Mar) (Box 21, Folder 621)
      - Wright, Richard (1959 Jul 2), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 622)
      - Wylie, Elinor (1922-28, n.d.) (Box 21, Folder 623)
      - Wylie, Jonathan (1971 Dec 4), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 624)
        Includes Wylie, Susanna
      - Yale Review (1940 Mar 15), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 625)
      - Yarmolinsky, Avrahm (1937-65), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 626)
        Includes Deutsch, Babette
      - Young, Stark (1948 Nov 15), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 627)
      - Zabel, Morton Dauwen (1931-63) (Box 21, Folder 628-630)
        Includes McCarthy, Mary
      - Zarudnaya, Elena (1956 May 8), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 631)
        See also: Levin, Harry, box 16, folder 483
      - Zigrosser, Carl (1923 Mar 24), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 632)
      - Zukovsky, Louis (1929 Dec 11), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 633)
      - Unidentified (1943-57), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 634)
    - Other Materials
      - Drafts, "Introduction," by Daniel Aaron, typescript photocopy, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 635)
      - Drafts, "Note to the Reader," by Elena Wilson, typescript and typescript photocopy (Box 21, Folder 636)
      - Drafts, translations of foreign quotations, holograph and typescript (Box 22, Folder 637-639)
      - Draft, index, typescript, corrected (Box 22, Folder 640)
      - Drafts, fragments, typescript, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 641)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 642-645)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 646-651)
      - Illustrations, drawings by Edmund Wilson, photocopies (Box 23, Folder 652)
      - Illustrations, reproductions of photographs and documents (Box 23, Folder 653-655)
        Includes photographs of Edmund Wilson and others
      - Illustrations, list, galley proof, photocopy, drafts of captions, and receipts for photographs (Box 23, Folder 656)
      - Setting copy, typescript, corrected, with proofreader's marks and printer's annotations, 1976 Mar (Box 24, Folder 657-663)
      - Setting copy, typescript, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1976 Mar (Box 25, Folder 664-665)
      - Galley proof, corrected, 1976 Nov (Box 25, Folder 666)
      - Galley proof, revised, corrected, 1977 Mar
      - Galley proofs, corrected, n.d.
      - Galley proof, revised, corrected, 1977 May 13 (Box 25, Folder 667)
      - Galley proof, holograph annotations, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 668)
      - Galley proof, fragment, annotations by Daniel Aaron, n.y. Dec 9
      - Galley proofs, fragments, corrected, 1976-77, n.d.
      - Page proofs, fragments, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 669)
      - Lists of corrections, holograph and typescript (Box 25, Folder 670)
      - Lists of corrections, by Leon Edel, typescript, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 671)
      - Lists of corrections by Farrar, Straus & Giroux, manuscript and typescript, 1976-77, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 672)
        Includes letters from Elena Wilson to FS&G
      - Advertisements, 1977-78 (Box 25, Folder 673)
      - Reviews, 1977-78, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 674-681)
      - Correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 25, Folder 682)
  - OTHER WRITINGS
    - "My View From the Other Window," draft, holograph (Box 26, Folder 683)
    - "My View From the Other Window," draft, typescript, corrected, signed, 1971-72 (Box 26, Folder 684)
    - Greek language notes, [1972-79] (Box 26, Folder 685-686)
    - Other notes, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 687)
  - WRITINGS BY OTHERS
    - Aaron, Daniel, lectures about Edmund Wilson, typescript carbon and photocopy (Box 26, Folder 688)
    - Aaron, Daniel, "The Letters of Edmund Wilson," clipping, Times Literary Supplement, 1977 May 20 (Box 26, Folder 689)
    - Aaron, Daniel, Letters on Literature and Politics, "Introduction"
      See: Writings/ Letters on Literature and Politics /Drafts, "Introduction," box 21, folder 635
    - Dabney, Lewis M., essay on Patriotic Gore, typescript mimeograph, 1976 Dec 28 (Box 26, Folder 690)
      See also: Correspondence, box 2, folder 63
    - Edel, Leon, "The Dead Sea Scrolls," typescript photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 691)
    - Edel, Leon, "Edmund Wilson: The Job Ahead," typescript photocopy, corrected (Box 26, Folder 692)
    - Edel, Leon, "The Madness of Art," offprint, American Journal of Psychiatry, 1975 Oct (Box 26, Folder 693)
    - Karlinsky, Simon, The Nabokov-Wilson Letters, contract with Elena Wilson, Vera Nabokova, and Harper & Row, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 694)
    - Karlinsky, Simon, The Nabokov-Wilson Letters, notes and corrections by Elena Wilson, holograph and typescript (Box 26, Folder 695)
    - Karlinsky, Simon, The Nabokov-Wilson Letters, draft, typescript photocopy, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 696-698)
    - Kazin, Alfred, "Alfred Kazin on Edmund Wilson: A View From the Sixties," clipping, photocopy, The New Republic, 1977 Oct 15 (Box 27, Folder 699)
    - Lamott, Kenneth Church, "Edmund Wilson in California: A Reappraisal," clipping, photocopy, The Nation, 1978 Jan 28 (Box 27, Folder 700)
    - Levin, Harry
      See: Subject Files/Edmund Wilson/ Other clippings, box 28, folder 710
    - Matthews, T. S. (Thomas Stanley)
    - Mele, Bette Crouse
      See: Correspondence, box 5, folder 178
    - Paul, Sherman, " Edmund Wilson, by Leonard Kriegel," book review, typescript, corrected (Box 27, Folder 701)
    - Rubenstein, Joshua, "Socialist Surrealism," clipping, photocopy, Commentary, 1977 ep (Box 27, Folder 702)
    - Struve, Marie, "Nevermore," memoir, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 703)
    - Unidentified, "For Elena on Easter," poem, manuscript, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 704)
- Subject Files, 1926-1978; Series III; 0.21; (1 box)
  - EDMUND WILSON
    - Biographical records, Princeton University, photocopies, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 705)
    - Lists and notes concerning copyright of books, typescript carbon and photocopy, 1977, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 706)
    - Lists of essays in The New Republic, 1920-41, typescript, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 707)
    - Notes concerning EW's death, manuscript, [1972] (Box 28, Folder 708)
    - Obituary, The New York Times, 1972 Jun 13 (Box 28, Folder 709)
    - Other clippings, 1973-75 (Box 28, Folder 710)
  - OTHER SUBJECTS
    - Barrytown, N. Y., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 711)
    - Edel, Leon, 1973, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 712)
    - Lhote, André, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 713)
    - Nevada, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 714)
    - O'Connor, Veniette, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 715)
    - Tolstoy family, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 716)
- Personal Papers, 1906-1073; Series IV; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Birth certificate, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 717)
  - Calendars, 1942-71 (Box 29, Folder 718-726)
  - Divorce records, 1946-70, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 727)
  - Passports, 1931-53 (Box 29, Folder 728-729)
    Includes photographs of Elena Wilson and Helen Miranda Wilson (child)
  - Social security records, 1969-73 (Box 29, Folder 730)
- Family Papers, 1910-1961; Series V; 0.1; (.5 box)
  - MUMM FAMILY
    - Mumm, Hermann, contract for marriage with Olga Struve, copies, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 731)
      Original dated 1904
    - Mumm, Walter, account of a balloon race in Stuttgart, Germany, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 732)
    - Struve, Olga
      See: Mumm, Hermann, box 30, folder 731
    - Other papers, 1948, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 733)
  - STRUVE FAMILY
    - Clippings, [1910]-61 (Box 30, Folder 734)
    - Genealogical tables, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 735)
  - THORNTON FAMILY
    - Thornton, Henry H. M., birth certificate, copy, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 736)
      Original dated 1932
    - Thornton, Henry, H. M., clipping about his marriage, 1957 Jun 9 (Box 30, Folder 737)
    - Thornton, James Worth, "Biographical Note", n.d. (Box 30, Folder 738)
- Helen Miranda Wilson Papers, 1979; Series VI; 0.1; (.5 box)
  - Will of Elena Wilson, copy, 1976 Apr 6 (Box 30, Folder 739)
  - Death certificate for Elena Wilson, copy, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 740)
    Original dated 1979
  - Obituary for Elena Wilson, [1979] (Box 30, Folder 741)
- Oversize, 9.67; (9 boxes)
  - Arbasino, Alberto (1961) (in Series II), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 742)
  - Dell, W. Stanley (1919-22) (in Series II) (Box 31, Folder 743)
  - Dell, W. Stanley (1922) (in Series II), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 744)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, illustrations, reproductions of photographs (in Series II) (Box 31, Folder 745)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proof, corrected (in Series II), 1976 Nov (Box 31, Folder 746)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, page proofs, fragments (in Series II) (Box 31, Folder 747)
  - Struve family, clippings (in Series V), [1910] (Box 31, Folder 748)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proof, revised, corrected (in Series II), 1976 Nov (Box 32, Folder 749)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proof, corrected (in Series II), 1977 Mar (Box 33, Folder 750)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proofs, corrected (in Series II) (Box 34, Folder 751)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proofs, corrected (in Series II) (Box 35, Folder 752)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proof, revised, corrected (in Series II), 1977 May 13 (Box 36, Folder 753)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proof, holograph annotations (in Series II) (Box 37, Folder 754)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proof, fragment, annotations by Daniel Aaron (in Series II), n.y. Dec 9 (Box 38, Folder 755)
  - Letters on Literature and Politics, galley proof, fragments, corrected (in Series II), 1976-77, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 756)
- Restricted Fragile, 1.04; (3 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 3 (Box 40, Folder 757)
  - Box 1, folder 9 (Box 40, Folder 758)
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 40, Folder 759)
  - Box 2, folder 39 (Box 40, Folder 760)
  - Box 2, folder 46 (Box 40, Folder 761)
  - Box 2, folder 63 (Box 40, Folder 762)
  - Box 2, folder 67 (Box 40, Folder 763)
  - Box 2, folder 80 (Box 40, Folder 764)
  - Box 2, folder 81 (Box 40, Folder 765)
  - Box 3, folder 98 (Box 40, Folder 766)
  - Box 3, folder 106 (Box 40, Folder 767)
  - Box 4, folder 125 (Box 40, Folder 768)
  - Box 4, folder 128 (Box 40, Folder 769)
  - Box 4, folder 149 (Box 40, Folder 770)
  - Box 4, folder 165 (Box 40, Folder 771)
  - Box 4, folder 171 (Box 40, Folder 772)
  - Box 4, folder 174 (Box 40, Folder 773)
  - Box 5, folder 186 (Box 40, Folder 774)
  - Box 5, folder 192 (Box 40, Folder 775)
  - Box 5, folder 195 (Box 40, Folder 776)
  - Box 5, folder 230 (Box 40, Folder 777)
  - Box 6, folder 261 (Box 40, Folder 778)
  - Box 6, folder 271 (Box 40, Folder 779)
  - Box 6, folder 274 (Box 40, Folder 780)
  - Box 6, folder 286 (Box 40, Folder 781)
  - Box 7, folder 287 (Box 40, Folder 782)
  - Box 7, folder 288 (Box 40, Folder 783)
  - Box 7, folder 289 (Box 40, Folder 784)
  - Box 7, folder 290 (Box 40, Folder 785)
  - Box 7, folder 291 (Box 40, Folder 786)
  - Box 7, folder 292 (Box 40, Folder 787)
  - Box 7, folder 293 (Box 40, Folder 788)
  - Box 7, folder 295 (Box 40, Folder 789)
  - Box 7, folder 296 (Box 40, Folder 790)
  - Box 7, folder 297 (Box 40, Folder 791)
  - Box 7, folder 299 (Box 40, Folder 792)
  - Box 8, folder 302 (Box 40, Folder 793)
  - Box 10, folder 319 (Box 40, Folder 794)
  - Box 10, folder 321 (Box 40, Folder 795)
  - Box 10, folder 323 (Box 40, Folder 796)
  - Box 10, folder 325 (Box 40, Folder 797)
  - Box 10, folder 330 (Box 40, Folder 798)
  - Box 10, folder 331 (Box 40, Folder 799)
  - Box 10, folder 335 (Box 40, Folder 800)
  - Box 11, folder 346 (Box 40, Folder 801)
  - Box 11, folder 353 (Box 40, Folder 802)
  - Box 12, folder 358 (Box 40, Folder 803)
  - Box 12, folder 359 (Box 40, Folder 804)
  - Box 12, folder 360 (Box 40, Folder 805)
  - Box 12, folder 364 (Box 40, Folder 806)
  - Box 12, folder 374 (Box 40, Folder 807)
  - Box 12, folder 375 (Box 40, Folder 808)
  - Box 12, folder 381 (Box 40, Folder 809)
  - Box 12, folder 382 (Box 40, Folder 810)
  - Box 12, folder 389 (Box 40, Folder 811)
  - Box 13, folder 395 (Box 40, Folder 812)
  - Box 13, folder 399 (Box 40, Folder 813)
  - Box 13, folder 404 (Box 40, Folder 814)
  - Box 13, folder 405 (Box 40, Folder 815)
  - Box 13, folder 412 (Box 40, Folder 816)
  - Box 13, folder 414 (Box 40, Folder 817)
  - Box 13, folder 415 (Box 40, Folder 818)
  - Box 13, folder 417 (Box 40, Folder 819)
  - Box 13, folder 421 (Box 40, Folder 820)
  - Box 13, folder 424 (Box 40, Folder 821)
  - Box 13, folder 426 (Box 40, Folder 822)
  - Box 14, folder 428 (Box 40, Folder 823)
  - Box 14, folder 429 (Box 40, Folder 824)
  - Box 14, folder 431 (Box 40, Folder 825)
  - Box 14, folder 435 (Box 40, Folder 826)
  - Box 14, folder 436 (Box 40, Folder 827)
  - Box 14, folder 437 (Box 40, Folder 828)
  - Box 14, folder 439 (Box 40, Folder 829)
  - Box 14, folder 449 (Box 40, Folder 830)
  - Box 14, folder 450 (Box 40, Folder 831)
  - Box 15, folder 453 (Box 40, Folder 832)
  - Box 15, folder 454 (Box 40, Folder 833)
  - Box 15, folder 457 (Box 40, Folder 834)
  - Box 15, folder 458 (Box 40, Folder 835)
  - Box 15, folder 459 (Box 41, Folder 836)
  - Box 15, folder 462 (Box 41, Folder 837)
  - Box 15, folder 463 (Box 41, Folder 838)
  - Box 15, folder 464 (Box 41, Folder 839)
  - Box 15, folder 467 (Box 41, Folder 840)
  - Box 15, folder 472 (Box 41, Folder 841)
  - Box 15, folder 478 (Box 41, Folder 842)
  - Box 15, folder 481 (Box 41, Folder 843)
  - Box 16, folder 483 (Box 41, Folder 844)
  - Box 16, folder 489 (Box 41, Folder 845)
  - Box 16, folder 491 (Box 41, Folder 846)
  - Box 16, folder 493 (Box 41, Folder 847)
  - Box 16, folder 494 (Box 41, Folder 848)
  - Box 16, folder 495 (Box 41, Folder 849)
  - Box 16, folder 500 (Box 41, Folder 850)
  - Box 16, folder 501 (Box 41, Folder 851)
  - Box 16, folder 503 (Box 41, Folder 852)
  - Box 16, folder 505 (Box 41, Folder 853)
  - Box 16, folder 510 (Box 41, Folder 854)
  - Box 17, folder 515 (Box 41, Folder 855)
  - Box 17, folder 517 (Box 41, Folder 856)
  - Box 17, folder 519 (Box 41, Folder 857)
  - Box 17, folder 524 (Box 41, Folder 858)
  - Box 17, folder 525 (Box 41, Folder 859)
  - Box 18, folder 529 (Box 41, Folder 860)
  - Box 18, folder 531 (Box 41, Folder 861)
  - Box 18, folder 536 (Box 41, Folder 862)
  - Box 18, folder 540 (Box 41, Folder 863)
  - Box 18, folder 543 (Box 41, Folder 864)
  - Box 19, folder 544 (Box 41, Folder 865)
  - Box 19, folder 551 (Box 41, Folder 866)
  - Box 19, folder 553 (Box 41, Folder 867)
  - Box 19, folder 560 (Box 41, Folder 868)
  - Box 19, folder 562 (Box 41, Folder 869)
  - Box 19, folder 563 (Box 41, Folder 870)
  - Box 19, folder 565 (Box 41, Folder 871)
  - Box 19, folder 567 (Box 41, Folder 872)
  - Box 19, folder 573 (Box 41, Folder 873)
  - Box 20, folder 575 (Box 41, Folder 874)
  - Box 20, folder 576 (Box 41, Folder 875)
  - Box 20, folder 580 (Box 41, Folder 876)
  - Box 20, folder 581 (Box 41, Folder 877)
  - Box 20, folder 583 (Box 41, Folder 878)
  - Box 20, folder 588 (Box 41, Folder 879)
  - Box 20, folder 590 (Box 41, Folder 880)
  - Box 20, folder 591 (Box 41, Folder 881)
  - Box 20, folder 592 (Box 41, Folder 882)
  - Box 20, folder 595 (Box 41, Folder 883)
  - Box 21, folder 607 (Box 41, Folder 884)
  - Box 21, folder 609 (Box 41, Folder 885)
  - Box 21, folder 610 (Box 41, Folder 886)
  - Box 21, folder 611 (Box 41, Folder 887)
  - Box 21, folder 612 (Box 41, Folder 888)
  - Box 21, folder 616 (Box 41, Folder 889)
  - Box 21, folder 617 (Box 41, Folder 890)
  - Box 21, folder 620 (Box 41, Folder 891)
  - Box 21, folder 626 (Box 41, Folder 892)
  - Box 21, folder 628 (Box 41, Folder 893)
  - Box 21, folder 631 (Box 41, Folder 894)
  - Box 21, folder 636 (Box 41, Folder 895)
  - Box 22, folder 637 (Box 41, Folder 896)
  - Box 22, folder 641 (Box 41, Folder 897)
  - Box 22, folder 642 (Box 41, Folder 898)
  - Box 22, folder 644 (Box 41, Folder 899)
  - Box 22, folder 645 (Box 41, Folder 900)
  - Box 23, folder 646 (Box 41, Folder 901)
  - Box 23, folder 647 (Box 41, Folder 902)
  - Box 23, folder 648 (Box 41, Folder 903)
  - Box 23, folder 649 (Box 41, Folder 904)
  - Box 23, folder 650 (Box 41, Folder 905)
  - Box 23, folder 651 (Box 41, Folder 906)
  - Box 23, folder 652 (Box 41, Folder 907)
  - Box 23, folder 655 (Box 41, Folder 908)
  - Box 23, folder 656 (Box 41, Folder 909)
  - Box 25, folder 665 (Box 42, Folder 910)
  - Box 25, folder 670 (Box 42, Folder 911)
  - Box 25, folder 672 (Box 42, Folder 912)
  - Box 25, folder 673 (Box 42, Folder 913)
  - Box 25, folder 674 (Box 42, Folder 914)
  - Box 25, folder 675 (Box 42, Folder 915)
  - Box 25, folder 676 (Box 42, Folder 916)
  - Box 25, folder 677 (Box 42, Folder 917)
  - Box 25, folder 678 (Box 42, Folder 918)
  - Box 25, folder 679 (Box 42, Folder 919)
  - Box 25, folder 680 (Box 42, Folder 920)
  - Box 26, folder 687 (Box 42, Folder 921)
  - Box 26, folder 688 (Box 42, Folder 922)
  - Box 26, folder 689 (Box 42, Folder 923)
  - Box 28, folder 709 (Box 42, Folder 924)
  - Box 28, folder 710 (Box 42, Folder 925)
  - Box 28, folder 711 (Box 42, Folder 926)
  - Box 28, folder 712 (Box 42, Folder 927)
  - Box 28, folder 715 (Box 42, Folder 928)
  - Box 28, folder 716 (Box 42, Folder 929)
  - Box 29, folder 727 (Box 42, Folder 930)
  - Box 30, folder 734 (Box 42, Folder 931)
  - Box 30, folder 737 (Box 42, Folder 932)
  - Box 30, folder 740 (Box 42, Folder 933)
  - Box 30, folder 741 (Box 42, Folder 934)
- Restricted Fragile Oversize, 1; (1 portfolio)
  - Box 23, folder 655 (Box Port, Folder 935)
  - Box 30, folder 735 (Box Port, Folder 936)
  - Box 31, folder 746 (Box Port, Folder 937)